Whether you're a fake using
his name or the real guy,
someday I'll kill you.
The first time Death Gun showed up was
after the second bullet of bullets.
And both of the murders he committed
happened in front of witnesses.
He's been staying under the
radar since the last killing,
probably leveling up as much as he can.
I don't see anyone
registered as Death Gun here,
but if he wants to stage another murder,
B .O .B.'s perfect, he'll be here.
I know it.
I gotta find out the name of
Death Gun's Avatar and stop him.
I'm still so happy with my sweet love.
I'm still so happy with my love.
How can I get hurt?
I'm still so happy with my sweet love.
I'm still so happy with my pain.
Oh?
xenon hello anyone home?
come on shut up!
i thought i made it
clear i was done talking.
god, what else?
do you want from me?
nothing but.
now that you mention it, maybe we could
swap some info before this starts.
i mean, like you know, for old times sake?
Fine, whatever.
I'll do it, even though I'm the one
who's going to be giving all the info.
But I got stuff to share, too.
It's not a lot, but still.
How are you feeling?
You think you got a shot this time?
By the time he sees me, it'll be too late.
This is crazy.
Yeah, the final is like one big party.
Yeah?
For only a thousand creds,
I can hook you up with top-secret
info on all the top players!
Here goes, all on Yamikaze.
I wonder what hookahs odds are.
Come on, Dyne.
Sure he's got good gear and solid skills,
but that dude's older than hell, you know?
At best, he'd come in 15th today.
If you want to go with a
long shot, go with Richie.
So, you think I'm too old to get it on?
No, I was just saying, this
old dog's got some nitrous.
Hey, look!
It's Kirito!
She hacks up people good
with that Botox sword.
Ooh, a hot berserker with a blade.
Xenon's weren't my type, brother.
I wouldn't mind getting
a bullet for Xenon.
Roger that.
I'd rather get slashed.
And go play ALO with the fairies.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, you're Kirito. Sorry.
Hey, guys.
Hope you're all rude for me.
Yeah, you got it. Good luck out there.
I bet my life savings on you.
Oh, God.
Quit messing with them.
Okay, so 30 players get dropped
randomly across the same map,
and then you go around
shooting whoever you
find and the winner's
the last one standing?
Oh man, I knew it.
You're gonna make me explain the
whole damn thing to you after all.
Don't you have email?
The admin sent the rules out, so
it should be sitting in your inbox.
Yeah, I did scan through it, but it's
like I wanted to make sure I understood.
There was a lot of info to absorb.
Absorb.
Basically, you pretty
much got the gist of it.
This thing's a battle royale
between 30 players on the same map.
Star points are random,
and players are dropped about
1,000 meters away from each other.
Whoa, a thousand?
That's got to be one insanely huge map.
Honestly, you didn't
read the email, did you?
It's a multi-stage arena,
10 kilometers in diameter.
It's got mountains, forests, and deserts.
The start time's afternoon,
so there's no advantage or disadvantage
in terms of gear or skills.
How can you find anyone
in a field that big?
That makes it challenging.
It's a game with gunfights, remember?
Anyway, players get an item
to track other players.
It's called a satellite scan terminal.
There's a satellite?
Like a spy drone or something? Yep.
It works just like in real life.
It passes overhead every 15 minutes.
It scans the arena and then
transmits the coordinates
of all the players
directly to your terminal.
Neat, huh?
Hmm.
So basically, you can only hide
in one spot for 15 minutes.
You catch on quick.
But then, doesn't all that moving
around put a sniper at a disadvantage?
Fifteen minutes is more than enough
time for a sniper to do their job.
I fire, I kill my target, I move on.
Oh, yeah, I guess.
So we good here? Great.
Next time we see each other,
you can bet your ass...
No, please, hold up, hold up!
Is there something else?
It's what I really want to talk about.
Hang on.
Could you take a look
at this list real quick?
Out of all the B .O .B.
contestants, are there any first-timers
whose names you don't recognize?
Okay, that's weird.
Please, just look at it and tell me.
It's important.
Well, if that's all you want
to know, I guess it's cool.
The first-timers I don't know, besides
a certain loser with a photon sword,
are three names.
That's great! Who? Point him out!
Jushi X, Pale Rider, and...
this guy.
Sterben?
Is one of them Death Gun?
You're going to tell me what this is about,
or are you going to keep me in the dark?
Getting ready to blow a fuse over here.
Speak up.
I swear, if you're trying to make
me mess up today by pissing me off,
I'm going to...
No, that's not it.
It's just that...
Does it have anything to do with
why you were acting weird yesterday?
You know, after the prelims?
It does.
Yesterday, this person I once played
against in another VR MMO came up to me.
I'm pretty sure one of the
names you pointed out is him.
Is he a friend of yours?
No. An enemy.
I can't remember his name, though.
And I think we tried to kill each other.
Kill each other?
For real?
Was it like an argument
with someone in your party?
Something like that? No way.
It wasn't that.
You don't kill someone over an argument.
Him and his group did horrible things.
Things like murder.
They were too far gone, and the
only way to stop them was by force.
I don't regret what I did,
but still, I've avoided
taking responsibility for it.
I forced myself to
forget it even happened.
For me,
there's no more running away, and this
time, I have to face what I did head-on.
Sorry to unload like that, just forget it.
Do you think you could still
pull the trigger, though?
Could you shoot a player
in here if you knew
in the real world that
player would die from it?
And what if you had to kill that player?
Because if you didn't, you or
someone you love would die.
If you had that power, could
you still pull that trigger?
Hirito, what's the name of
the game you met this guy in?
Sorry, never mind. That's personal.
No, that's okay.
Kirito
I
Sinon?
We should start heading over
to the waiting dome now.
We have to check our gear.
And get ourselves psyched
up for this battle.
Yeah, sure.
Lead the way.
I get you've got your
reasons for being here.
Just like me.
But.
It's got nothing to do
with that promise you made.
I gotta pay you back.
For what happened in yesterday's final?
Well, got it?
You owe me a fight, so
you better stay alive.
Roger that.
I promise I'll survive and
give you the fight you want.
Thanks.
If you're a battle junkie who loves
the smell of gun oil and gun smoke,
then get ready!
Place your bets, because
we're about to start!
Now,
are you guys ready to find out who's
the strongest player in Gun Gale Online,
the hardest game in town?
As usual, MMO Stream will be broadcasting
the battle live and uncensored.
All right, help me out
with the countdown, guys.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6,
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
The third bullet of bullets has begun!
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Bingo.
Alright! Yeah! You go, girl!
Twenty-one survivors left in play.
Looks like Dine's on the run.
Richie's got a heavy machine gun.
So he'll sit tight.
He likes his prey coming to him.
I'll go after Dine and Pale Rider.
I wonder how he's doing out there?
What the hell do I care?
Damn, this guy's freaking persistent.
Come on.
I got a mag full of rounds
with your name on them.
You forgot to check your six again, Dine.
See you later.
Who's there?
Shh.
Keep it down.
I need a favor. Are you kidding?
It's too late for any more favors.
One of us dies right now.
Stop it.
I don't want those guys
to know we're here.
What are you up to?
I want to watch what
happens on that bridge.
So don't shoot, okay?
Okay.
Then what? That depends.
But I'm not here for you.
I'll leave after.
Promise.
The minute you turn your
back, I'll blow you away.
If that's what you want, then fine.
But for now, just stay quiet.
All right.
But after they're done down
there, it's you and me.
Okay.
Your stealth skills are pretty pathetic.
I'm not letting him leave the area alive!
If he makes a move, I'm taking the shot.
He's all yours.
Wait, company?
Oh, son of a...
Damn it!
Whoa, he's fast.
He boosted his three-dimensional
mobility by carrying lighter gear.
His acrobatic skills are through the roof!
Bastard!
Gah!
No!
If only he had time to switch mags,
he could have shot from the
hip and killed him easy.
That pale guy.
He's quick and powerful.
Maybe he's the one in the cloak.
An enemy.
I think we tried to kill
each other once before.
I'm taking him out.
Okay, but it won't be
easy if he's who I think.
Oh, please.
He can't dodge my bullet at this range.
Did you hear a gunshot?
There wasn't one.
What the hell's going on?
Two possibilities.
It could have been a laser
rifle with a muffled blast.
Or maybe a live ammo gun with a silencer.
Either way, it wasn't a kill shot.
So why isn't he moving?
I think the shot came from the forest.
Uh-uh.
He was sniped from further away than that.
I did a scan of the map not too long ago.
There's no one within
one kilometer of here.
And now that we're on the subject, you
mind telling me where you came from?
Uh, I was chasing after
that pale rider guy.
Hang on.
Oh, no way. What's up?
When the satellite was scanning the
area, I was swimming in that river.
I guess my location didn't register
on the map because I was underwater.
Was all that gear?
You should have drowned.
Nah, I took it all off before I dove in.
Stuck it in my item storage.
I never knew we could use the
river for cover from the satellite.
Thanks for the tip.
I'll keep it in mind.
Xenon, check out his shoulder.
There's a weird light there.
A stun bullet!
How long's he been there?
He's got a silent assassin.
Is that what his rifle's called?
Yeah.
It's a high-end sniper rifle
that's got a badass silencer on it.
I heard rumors about there being one
in GGO, but I've never seen it before.
If he can handle that gun,
he must be some player.
Why would he use his
handgun to finish him off?
Xenon, shoot! Huh? Which one?
It's the guy in the cloak!
There's no time!
Shoot him!
Hurry!
Don't let him fire that gun!
Sugou kieru nukumori Nori
hi to tsunomai yoranai
yo Mito kuyoku to tsuyoku
Knight to mega ta Kukamimi
mo kakagellu Kodok na
koshino Yuna koko no Back ku
Next time, Death Gun.
Thank you.